http://www.warriortablesoccer.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Warrior Table Soccer and its affiliates (hereinafter referred to as The Company) respects the privacy needs and concerns of our customers. That is why how we handle any personal information, such as your name, address, email address or phone number (“Personal Information”) that you provide to us is important to us. This Privacy Statement describes the Personal Information we gather about you, what we do with it, the safeguards we have in place to protect it, and how you can control our use of it. By using the Sites, the user agrees, without limitation or qualification, to be bound by this Privacy Statement.
When you provide Personal Information at our Call Centers, and our Sites, you are consenting to the manner in which The Company will collect, use, disclose and otherwise manage your Personal Information, as set out below.
Financial information that we collect is used to bill customers for products and services, as well as check The Company’s partners’ qualifications for registration. Unique identifiers (such as Social Security numbers or tax ID numbers) are collected to be used only in the reporting of income tax when The Company partner may have received in excess of $600.00 during a fiscal year (this amount is subject to change by the federal government of the United States). This information may differ for residents of other nations. Demographic and profile data may also be collected by our site. We use this data to tailor our visitors’ experience at our site by showing them content that we think they might be interested in and displaying the content according to their preferences. This is designed to enhance the shopping experience.
Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitors’ contact information (e-mail address) and financial information (account or credit card numbers). We may also collect demographic information (zip code, age, or income level).
At times, The Company may conduct user surveys. When we do, we gather that information in order to help evolve our business model. We may share or sell that information with business partners. We may, at times, use the demographic information we gathered as a marketing or promotional tool.
The Company also allows any customer to create a customer account. This allows the user to simplify his or her purchase process at any of The Company’s sites. All the information that a customer supplies during account creation will be held in the strictest confidence. It will be used to manage the payment and shipping of orders.
From time to time, we also use the information you provide about yourself or others to inform you of additions or improvements to The Company’s services, as well as conduct member surveys in order to improve our services in the form of various communication platforms including, but not limited to email, phone, and text messages.
Who May Use the Sites
The Sites are not intended or designed to attract users under the age of 18. We do not collect Personal Information from any person we know to be under the age of 18. If you are under 18, we ask that you not send us any Personal Information.
The Sites are intended for users from the United States and those not governed by privacy policies of other countries. Information sent to us will be housed on servers located in the United States. Do not send us information unless you consent to the application of U.S law and to the use and disclosure of your information consistent with this Privacy Statement.
Collection and Use of Personal Information
We may collect Personal Information that you provide us when you:
Purchase, order, return, exchange or request certain information about our products and services;
Contact a Call Center or customer service desk;
Visit or register with our Sites or participate in another feature of our Sites
Enter into a contest or sweepstakes or respond to one of our surveys; or
Provide us with comments or suggestions.
We may also collect Personal Information about you from our Service Providers who provide us with e-commerce related services related to the Sites.
Call Centers
When you call one of our Call Centers about a product, delivery, billing question or for customer service, you may be asked for Personal Information that identifies you along with additional information we need to help us promptly answer your question, such as your name and address and a phone number where we might contact you. We may retain this information to assist you in the future.
Site Registration
Registration is an optional service provided by our Sites. When you register, you are asked for information such as your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, and your interests, if you choose to register them. Your registration information may be used to help make your online shopping quicker and easier, by pre-filling certain parts of your shopping information. When you register you will have the opportunity to sign up for future marketing information from The Company.
Contests, Questions or Surveys
When you ask a question, participate in a survey or enter a contest or sweepstakes at The Company’s sponsored event or through our Sites, we may collect your name, address, phone number and e-mail address. We use this information to administer your participation in a contest or sweepstakes. At the time you are entering a contest or sweepstakes, we may ask your permission to send you future marketing information from The Company.
Other Uses of Personal Information
The Company also uses Personal Information, including information provided to us from our Service Providers, to continually assess and improve the products and services we offer. To serve you better, we may combine the Personal Information that you give us with publicly available information and information we receive from or cross-reference with our marketing partners and others. We use that combined information to enhance and personalize your shopping experience with us, to communicate with you about our products and events that may be of interest to you, and for other promotional purposes.
Promotional Information and Marketing Materials
We would like to inform you of products and services, sales and special offers that might benefit you. When you register online or participate in a survey, you will have the opportunity to sign up for e-mails about our products, services, sales and special offers.
We may also send you mail, email or call you with information about our product and service offerings if you have provided us with your name and address, email address or phone numbers at our Sites or Call Centers. If you would like to stop receiving such promotional information from The Company, please see the “Privacy Preferences/Opt-Out” section of this Privacy Statement.
Disclosure of Personal Information
We enter into marketing relationships with advertisers or other companies that provide products or services that we believe may be of interest to The Company’s customers. We will share your Personal Information with those marketing partners in order to help them send you information that we believe will be of interest to you. We may share non-identifiable aggregated information with these companies. We will not disclose your credit card account information for these purposes. We may also provide Personal Information to any of our affiliated businesses.
Access to Personal Information by Companies that Work with or on Behalf of The Company
Some of our operations, such as our electronic commerce, may be managed by Service Providers who are unaffiliated companies. These companies may share Personal Information with their affiliates and with service providers whom they engage to perform services related to our Sites or the operation of our business. Examples of these services include payment processing and authorization, fraud protection and credit risk reduction, product customization, order fulfillment and shipping, marketing and promotional material distribution, Web site evaluation, data analysis and, where applicable, data cleansing. These companies may have access to your Personal Information on a confidential basis only to the extent necessary to perform their functions. In no event will we authorize these companies to use your Personal Information for any reason other than to provide you with those specific services.
If your purchases are being shipped to you, your shipping information will be shared with our delivery service providers (U.S. Postal Service, FedEx, or other delivery companies we or you select). Our delivery service providers are asked not to use your Personal Information for any purpose other than making the delivery.
Sale of Business
In the event that The Company or some of our assets are sold or transferred or used as security, your Personal Information may be transferred to third parties as part of that transaction.
Disclosures of Personal Information in Legal Proceedings
If The Company or any of our Service Providers is requested by law enforcement officials or judicial authorities to provide Personal Information on individual users, The Company or the applicable Service Provider may, without your consent, provide such information. In matters involving claims of personal or public safety, The Company or the applicable Service Provider may provide your Personal Information to appropriate authorities without your consent or court process. The Company or our Service Providers also will provide your Personal Information in response to a search warrant or other legally valid inquiry or order, or to an investigative body in the case of a breach of an agreement or contravention of law, or in litigation involving The Company, the applicable Service Provider, or otherwise as required by law. We may also disclose Personal Information to assist in debt collection where you owe a debt to us.
Access to Personal Information
You may request access to the Personal Information that we have about you. For further instructions on accessing the Personal Information that The Company may have about you, please see the “Contacting Us” section of this Privacy Statement.
ADDITIONAL INFORMATION ABOUT OUR SITES
Visiting Our Sites
In general, you can visit our Sites without telling us who you are or providing us with any information. However, we collect the IP (Internet protocol) addresses of all visitors to our Sites and other related information such as page requests, browser type, operating system and average time spent on our Sites. We use this information to monitor and improve our Sites.
Cookies and Tracer Tags
Our Sites use a technology called “cookies”. A cookie is a tiny element of data that our Sites can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your hard drive so we can recognize you when you return. All pages on our Sites where you are prompted to log in or that are customizable require that you accept cookies. If you have registered with our Sites, these cookies (1) may let us know who you are, (2) are necessary to access your account information (stored on our computers) in order to deliver products and personalized services, and (3) will provide us and our Service Providers with information that we will use to personalize our Sites in accordance with your preferences. Cookies are also required to optimize your shopping experience in that they allow you to add multiple items to your shopping basket before checking out. You may set your Web browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. However, should you decide not to accept cookies from our Sites, you will limit the functionality we can provide when you visit our Sites.
We also use cookies to improve the performance of our advertising on other websites.
Security of Personal Information
We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect against unauthorized access, use, modification and disclosure of Personal Information in our custody and control. We also are committed to employing reasonable technology in order to protect the security of our Sites. However, even with the best technology, no website is 100% secure. We will take reasonable measures which we believe are appropriate to protect your Personal Information from loss, misuse, alteration or destruction, and, where possible, will ask that any third parties to whom we may transfer such information to take comparable steps to protect that security.
Secure Shopping
When you place orders on our Sites, all of your order information, including your card number and delivery address, is transmitted through the Internet using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. SSL technology causes your browser to encrypt your order information before transmitting it to our secure server. SSL technology, an industry standard, is designed to prevent someone other than operators of our Sites from capturing and viewing your Personal Information. Since any order information you provide to us on our Sites will be transmitted using a secure connection, if your Web browser cannot support this level of security, you will not be able to order products through our Sites.
Our Privacy Statement and Outside Links
This Privacy Statement only applies to the various Sites. Our Sites may include links to the websites of our business partners, vendors and advertisers. These other sites are outside of our control. Please be aware that these websites may collect information about you, and operate according to their own privacy practices which may differ from those contained in our Privacy Statement. Remember to consult that website’s own privacy policy, as once you are outside any of the Sites, any information you submit is no longer in our control.
Privacy Statement Modifications
From time to time we may modify or amend this Privacy Statement in order to comply with new laws or regulations or to reflect future changes in our business practices. Any changes in our policies will be communicated in this page so please check back on occasion. We also may post a notice on our Sites or send an email describing the changes.
Contacting Us
If you have any questions about our handling of Personal Information, please contact us at Warrior Table Soccer, 15801 Rockfield Blvd. Suite J. Irvine, CA 92618 or e-mail us cs@warriortablesoccer.com. Alternatively, you may call us 1-866-436-6722.
For additional information, contact Warrior Table Soccer Client Services by email or by phone at 1-866-436-6722.
Monday – Friday:
10:00 am – 6:00 pm PST
Local Pick Ups Available in Irvine CA & Hesperia CA please call for more details.
